[{
  "answer": "Maria",
  "category": "Law",
  "question": "Sienna law forbids women of named what from prostitution?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "one eighth inch per hour",
  "category": "Anatomy",
  "question": "How fast do sperm swim?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Free Vasectomies",
  "category": "anatomy",
  "question": "What was given out to celebrate the birthday of King Bjumbal in Thailand in 1983?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Lysistrata",
  "category": "Culture",
  "question": "The women refuse sex in which one of Aristophanes plays?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Doucet",
  "category": "Animal Anatomy",
  "question": "What is a a stags Testicle called?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Novelty Condoms",
  "category": "Shopping",
  "question": "What are the most often ordered item from sex catalogues?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Masturbating",
  "category": "Freaky",
  "question": "According to Hite report women like to use candles for what?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "58%",
  "category": "Freaky",
  "question": "What percentage of people like dirty talk during sex?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Have Multiple Orgasms",
  "category": "Freaky",
  "question": "30% of women have done it but only 10% do what regularly",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Fritz the cat",
  "category": "Entertainment",
  "question": "What was the world's first X rated cartoon?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Less than 2 inches",
  "category": "Animal Anatomy",
  "question": "A Gorilla has how long of an erect penis?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Syphilis",
  "category": "Disease",
  "question": " If your doctor gives you salversan he is treating you for what?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Caressing in bed without intercourse",
  "category": "Fetishes",
  "question": "What sort of sexual practice is Lectamia?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "A barnacle",
  "category": "Animal Anatomy",
  "question": "What creature has a penis 20 times the length of its body?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "10%",
  "category": "Anatomy",
  "question": "What percentage of men claim to Shave their pubic hair regularly?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Mr. Spock",
  "category": "Entertainment",
  "question": "What TV character must have sex every 7 years?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Vagina",
  "category": "Ancient Languages",
  "question": "What English word comes from Latin for Sheath for a Sword?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Food in sex play",
  "category": "Philia",
  "question": "A Sitophilliac gets sexually aroused from what?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": " A Butterfly",
  "category": "Adult Toys",
  "question": "What is the name for a special vibrator worn with straps?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Gonorrhea",
  "category": "Disease",
  "question": "Every day 2,700 Americans find out that they have what disease?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "They were bisexuals",
  "category": "Famous People",
  "question": "What did Socrates,  Aristotle, and  Janis Joplin have in common?",
  "value": "1000"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Once every seven seconds",
  "category": "men",
  "question": "How often does an verage adult male think of sex?",
  "value": "300"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Wisconsin",
  "category": "Law",
  "question": "In which Great Lakesâ€™s state is it illegal for a man to shoot off a gun while his female partner has an orgasm?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Sex",
  "category": "Relaxation",
  "question": "According to Playboy, what is 10 times more effective than Valium as a tranquilizer?",
  "value": "200"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Hymen",
  "category": "Anatomy",
  "question": "Which part of the female anatomy shares its name with the Greek God of Marriage Ceremonies?",
  "value": "500"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Dolly Parton",
  "category": "Famous People",
  "question": "Which well known entertainer reportedly has her breasts insured for $600,000?",
  "value": "300"
}
,
{
  "answer": "34%",
  "category": "Women's Lingerie",
  "question": "What percent of American women prefer to match their bra and panties?",
  "value": "500"
}
,
{
  "answer": "14%",
  "category": "Freaky",
  "question": "Within 2%...According to an ABC News Poll, what percentage of American adults have had a threesome? ",
  "value": "500"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Mississippi",
  "category": "Statistics",
  "question": "What U.S. state has the lowest legal marriage age, allowing females to marry without parental consent at the age of 15?",
  "value": "500"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Wet Dreams",
  "category": "Phobia",
  "question": "Oneirogmophobia is a fear of?",
  "value": "400"
}
,
{
  "answer": "22%",
  "category": "Freaky",
  "question": "According to the Kinsey Institute, what percentage of women in their 20s have engaged in anal sex within the past year?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": "A dental Dam",
  "category": "Sex Gear",
  "question": "What is a square piece of latex that protects you against STI's when performing oral sex on a female?",
  "value": "300"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Nothing",
  "category": "Stimulants",
  "question": "What is the best thing to do when trying to sober up after having to much to drink?",
  "value": "400"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Depoprovera",
  "category": "Birth Control",
  "question": "This injectable hormone prevents pregnancy for up to three months.",
  "value": "100"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Contact with buttocks",
  "category": "Phillia",
  "question": "If you had Psygophillia what would arouse you?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Masturbation",
  "category": "Definition",
  "question": "What is ipsism another name for?",
  "value": "600"
}
,
{
  "answer": " Stretching the vagina",
  "category": "Defintion",
  "question": "Kolpeuryntomania is what sexual activity?",
  "value": "600"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Condoms",
  "category": "Law",
  "question": "In Elko Nevada sex without what is illegal?",
  "value": "600"
}
,
{
  "answer": "It's the average amount of semen in an ejaculation",
  "category": "Organization",
  "question": "Where did the group 10cc get their name?",
  "value": "900"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Parked Car",
  "category": "Definition",
  "question": "Amomaxia is having sex while in a what?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": "37%",
  "category": "Statistics",
  "question": "What percentage  of women prefer shoe shopping to sex?",
  "value": "900"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Female Genitals",
  "category": "Religion",
  "question": " Yoni worshipers worship what?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": " Fellatio",
  "category": "Feaky",
  "question": "Irrumation is what sexual practice?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": " Pompeii",
  "category": "Ancient Culture",
  "question": "A Winged Penis was the city symbol of what city?",
  "value": "800"
}
,
{
  "answer": "Crowds",
  "category": "Definition",
  "question": "An Ochlophilliac gets sexually aroused from what Being in what?",
  "value": "700"
}
,
{
  "answer": "6 calories",
  "category": "Fact",
  "question": "On average, how many calories are in a single ejaculation?",
  "value": "800"
}
]
